Guide to the Rice University Smalley Institute for Nanoscale Science and Technology records, 1993-2015 UA 184
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series VII: Audio & Video/ Computer disks, 1995-2010
  - Office CD's (64) and DVD's (27), 2000-2010 (Box 13, Case 2)
    - Smalley Bib March 2007, 2002-2007 (Box 13, Case 2)
    - Tuna Fest - Smalley Institute, June, 2007 (Box 13, Case 2)
    - Tunafest 2007 (Box 13, Case 2)
    - NASA*RICE Nucleation and Growth Workshop III at Canyon of the Eagles Lodge April 15-19, 2007 (Box 13, Case 2)
    - Rice Nanochemistry Academy 2007 (Box 13, Case 2)
    - Rice IPC-NET 2007 (Box 13, Case 2)
    - Aerospace Electrical and Energy Systems January 22-23, 2007, Disc 1 of 5 (Box 13, Case 2)
    - Aerospace Electrical and Energy Systems January 22-23, 2007, Disc 2 of 5 (Box 13, Case 2)
    - Aerospace Electrical and Energy Systems January 22-23, 2007, Disc 3 of 5 (Box 13, Case 2)
    - Aerospace Electrical and Energy Systems January 22-23, 2007, Disc 4 of 5 (Box 13, Case 2)
    - Aerospace Electrical and Energy Systems January 22-23, 2007, Disc 5 of 5 (Box 13, Case 2)
    - CNL FY07 Spreadsheets, 2006 (Box 13, Case 2)
    - First International Symposium on Nanotechnology, Energy, and Space Presentations October 25-28, 2009, 2010 (Box 13, Case 2)
    - Nanotech Conference & Expo 2009 Technical Proceedings Vol. 1-3 (Box 13, Case 2)
    - Clean Technology Conference & Expo 2009 Technical Proceedings (Box 13, Case 2)
    - Year of the Nano Group 2 Animation, 2010 (Box 13, Case 2)
    - Year of the Nano Group 1 Animation, 2010 (Box 13, Case 2)
    - Pablo's Work Jan. 2010 Kinkaid (Box 13, Case 2)
    - Kilby/Smalley The Promise of Tommorow [sic], 2006 (Box 13, Case 2)
    - Compilation DVD: Small Is Big, Concept Development, CBEN Teacher Internship, Nanokids Nanochem, 2007 (Box 13, Case 2)
    - Nano mdb (access of nanop db), 2005 (Box 13, Case 2)
    - Smalley Files from Valene, 2009 (Box 13, Case 2)
    - Nano Kids Movie, 2006 (Box 13, Case 2)
    - Energy Univ. Prof. Talk Jan 23, 2003 (PPTs) (Box 13, Case 2)
    - Romeos 4/11/03, 2003 (Box 13, Case 2)
    - MIT Forum Part 1 Part 2 Jan 22, 2003 Smalley & Simmons (PPTs) (Box 13, Case 2)
    - Presentations May 2003 (Box 13, Case 2)
    - DURINT PPTs 02.03.03, 2003 (Box 13, Case 2)
    - DURINT CD Final, 2001-2004 (Box 13, Case 2)
    - Nano Summit 2003 July 31, 2003, 2001-2003 (Box 13, Case 2)
    - Rice NASA Workshop February 28 through March 2, 2003 (Box 13, Case 2)
    - "Our Energy Challenge" Richard E. Smalley Columbia University 9/23/03, 2003 (Box 13, Case 2)
    - Energy and Nanotechnology: Strategy for the Future DVD 1: May 2, 2003 Kay Baily Hutchinson [sic] May 3, 2003 8:00 am - 2:17 pm (Box 13, Case 2)
    - Energy and Nanotechnology: Strategy for the Future DVD 2: May 3, 2003 3:22 pm - 5:00 pm, May 4, 2003, 8:00 am - 2:17 pm (Box 13, Case 2)
    - Energy and Nanotechnology: Strategy for the Future DVD 3: May 4, 2003 2:17 pm - 6:00 pm (Box 13, Case 2)
    - Collaborative Environments for Scientific Research, 2003 (Box 13, Case 2)
    - Smalley Group Website 6 Aug 2002 (Box 13, Case 2)
    - NNI Program 5/02, 2002 (Box 13, Case 2)
    - NNI Pics + Presentations, 2002 (Box 13, Case 2)
    - SMU Nano ppt 10/16/02, 2002 (Box 13, Case 2)
    - U&M / Facilities, 2003 (Box 13, Case 2)
    - National Nanotechnology Initiative Southern Regional Workshop Disc 1, 2002 (Box 13, Case 2)
    - National Nanotechnology Initiative Southern Regional Workshop Disc 2, 2002 (Box 13, Case 2)
    - National Nanotechnology Initiative Southern Regional Workshop Disc 3, 2002 (Box 13, Case 2)
    - DURINT July 9-10, 2001, 2000-2001 (Box 13, Case 2)
    - MMETS Lecture, Richard Smalley, 2009 (Box 13, Case 2)
    - Smalley PDF Publications, 2003-2004 (Box 13, Case 2)
    - Boris Yakobson CNL DOE3 Project, 2006 (Box 13, Case 2)
    - CNST Intro, 2002 (Box 13, Case 2)
    - CNST/CBEN, 2002 (Box 13, Case 2)
    - Nano Solar Presentations, 2001-2004 (Box 13, Case 2)
    - The First International Symposium on Nanotechnology, Energy and Space, 2009 (Box 13, Case 2)
    - Nanotechnology Venture Forum, 2007 (Box 13, Case 2)
    - Nano Vivo Conference, 2002-2005 (Box 13, Case 2)
    - Quest for Excellence, 2002 (Box 13, Case 2)
    - Houston We Have a Problem (Watermarked Screener), 2009 (Box 13, Case 2)
    - Rice University Virtual Tour of the Wiess School of Natural Sciences, 2005 (Box 13, Case 2)
  - Photos on CD's (21) and DVD's (4), 2000-2010 (Box 13, Case 3)
    - Art Car Parade 2010 (Box 13, Case 3)
    - Rice Nano Gala 2010 Cam #1 7:00 PM - 9:00 PM (Box 13, Case 3)
    - Tunafest 2006 6/30/2006 Pics by Dick Granoff (Box 13, Case 3)
    - Giant Nano Tube Disk 1 4-22-05, 2005 (Box 13, Case 3)
    - GMW05 Pictures 4/26/05, 2004-2005 (Box 13, Case 3)
    - Nanotube 4/22/05, 2005 (Box 13, Case 3)
    - Longest Nanotube in the World! 4/22/05, 2005 (Box 13, Case 3)
    - Richard Smalley Photos 21 Sept 2000, 2009 (Box 13, Case 3)
    - Smalley & Curl Photos, 2003 (Box 13, Case 3)
    - Nichol Pic, 2007 (Box 13, Case 3)
    - Clean Room event pics, 2004 (Box 13, Case 3)
    - Curl + Smalley pics, 2003 (Box 13, Case 3)
  - Nano digital video cassettes (54), Rice Nano Gala on DVCAM, 2010 (Box 13, Case 4)
  - Computer disc media analysis forms for media in boxes 12-13 (Box 13a)
- Series VIII: Oversize materials, 1996-2011
  - Buckyballs: Photographs and Negative (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Nanoart Contest Poster, 2011 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Framed Photographs of Nobel Prize team, 1996 (Box 14, Item 3)
  - Proclamations, 2005-2010 (Box 14, Folder 4)